http://www.vitecmm.com/privacy-policy

VITEC Digital Video Innovations -Privacy PolicySkip navigation VITEC Commits to Becoming Carbon Neutral by 2021 > Read more VITEC shakes up ISR mission with credit card size, low bandwidth HEVC Encoder > Read more> Background> Locations> Careers> Events> Success Stories> Green Initiative Blog
Reset
Privacy Policy IntroductionVITEC takes the privacy and protection of your personal information very seriously. We will only use your personal information in a lawful and fair manner. We will only collect information where it is necessary for us to do so and we will only collect information if it is relevant when dealing with you. This Privacy Policy explains how and for what purposes we use the information collected about you through this website, the VITEC Support Portal, and during the recruiting process. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time to take account of changing requirements, and we request that you refer back to this Policy frequently to review any revision. VITEC, 99 rue Pierre Sémard, 92320 Chatillon is the data controller under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (‘GDPR’) and has designated a data protection officer who can be contacted at privacy(at)vitec.com.If you have any query regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy(at)vitec.com. Collection of Your Personal InformationAs part of our activities, we collect and maintain your personal information. For example: When you register on our website to request information or a login to the Support Portal, you may provide us with certain personal information including your name and email address.To login to the VITEC Support Portal, you will also be asked to choose a unique password, which will be used solely for the purpose of providing access to your user account.During the recruiting process, by applying per email to a job opening you may provide us with personal information.You may provide us with information in the course of customer support interactions, email exchanges and surveys.We use the Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, files accessed, errors generated, time zone, operating system and other visitor details collected in our log files to analyze visit trends, administer the website, track visitor's movements and to improve our website. We link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.We also collect data via cookies (see section below).We use your personal information for specified, explicit and legitimate purposes. For example:To provide you with information about a VITEC product or service which you requested.To provide you with other information relating to our products, services or events, which we believe could be of interest to you.To invite you to participate in events held by us or by third parties, in surveys and seek your views in relation to VITEC’s products and services.To analyze online experience of visitors for marketing purposes in order to improve our products and services. Cookies and Other Tracking TechnologiesWe use temporary and permanent cookies to enhance your experience of our services. Temporary cookies will be removed from your computer each time you close your browser. By selecting ‘keep me signed-in’ option in VITEC services, a permanent cookie will be stored in your computer and you will not be required to sign-in by providing complete login information each time you return to our website. If you have turned cookies off, you may not be able to use registered areas of the website. We tie cookie information to your email address when you elect to remain logged in so as to maintain and recall your preferences within the website.Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by VITEC and our partners [such as reseller partners], affiliates, or service providers [such as analytics service providers]. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.You can prevent the setting of cookies by adjusting the settings on your browser (see your browser’s Help for how to do this). Be aware that disabling cookies will affect the functionality of this and many other websites that you visit. Disabling cookies will usually result in also disabling certain functionality and features.How can I change my VITEC cookie settings?You can prevent the setting of cookies by adjusting the settings on your browser (see your browser’s Help for how to do this). Be aware that disabling cookies will affect the functionality of this and many other websites that you visit. Disabling cookies will usually result in also disabling certain functionality and features.Some options may be selected below.Strictly necessary cookiesThese cookies are essential so that you can move around the website and use its features. Without these cookies services you have asked for cannot be provided.Functional cookiesThese cookies allow the website to remember choices you make to give you better functionality and personal features.Analytics cookiesThese cookies help to analyze the usage of the VITEC website. Links from our WebsiteSome pages of our website contain external links. You are advised to verify the privacy practices of such other websites. We are not responsible for the manner of use or misuse of information made available by you at such other websites. We encourage you not to provide personal information, without assuring yourselves of the Privacy Policy of such other websites. Sharing of InformationVITEC being a global company, we may need to share your personal information to our affiliates, resellers, service providers solely for the purpose of providing our products and services to you. The purposes for which we may disclose your personal information or data to our service providers may include, but are not limited to, data storage, database management, web analytics and payment processing. These service providers are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. In such cases VITEC will also ensure that such selected third-parties comply with this Privacy Policy and adopt appropriate confidentiality and security measures. Other than as set out above, we will not disclose any of your personal information without your permission unless we are required by law to do so. Transferring your Information Outside of the European Economic Area (“EEA”)In some instances personal data may be transferred to countries outside the EEA. For example, this may happen if one of our service providers is located in a country outside the EEA. We also share information between our affiliates, business partners, or other carefully selected third parties which may be located in other countries worldwide. Countries outside the EEA may not have similar data protection laws to those within the EEA. If we transfer your information outside of the EEA in this way, we will take steps to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected. Information SecurityWe ensure data protection compliance across the organization through:Implementing appropriate technical and organizational measures including internal data protection policies, staff training, internal audits of processing activities, and reviews of HR practices.Maintaining relevant documentation on processing activities.Implementing appropriate data protection by design, data collection, storage and processing security measures, as well as physical security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information. Your RightsIf you wish to exercise your rights to access, correct, update or remove any personal information, you may do so either by accessing your user profile or by contacting us at privacy@vitec.com. You also have the right to object to direct marketing.In accordance with local law in your region, you may have additional rights regarding the processing of your personal information. For example under GDPR, you have the following specific rights in respect of the personal data we process:The right to be informed about how we use personal data. This Privacy Policy explains who we are; the purposes for which we process personal data and our legitimate interests in doing so; the categories of data we process; third party disclosures; and details of any transfers of personal data outside the EEA.The right to erasure of personal data, to restriction of processing, right to data portability, right to object and right in relation to automated decision making and profiling.In the event we decide to use your personal information for any purpose other than as stated in this Privacy Policy, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of your personal information for those other purposes. From time to time, we may send emails to you regarding new services, releases and upcoming events. You may opt out of receiving newsletters and other secondary messages from VITEC by selecting the ‘unsubscribe’ function present in every email we send. However, you will continue to receive essential transactional emails. Retention PeriodWe will only keep your information for as long as we are either required to by law or as it is relevant for the purposes for which it was collected. We maintain a data retention policy in this respect. Enforcement of Privacy PolicyWe make every effort, including periodic reviews to ensure that personal information provided by you is used in conformity with this Privacy Policy. If you have any concern regarding our adherence to this Privacy Policy or the manner in which personal information is used for the purpose of providing our services, contact privacy(at)vitec.com. We will contact you to address your concerns and we will also cooperate with regulatory authorities in this regard if needed.You have the right to lodge a complaint to the supervisory authority of VITEC’s main establishment:CNIL (Commission Nationale de l'Informatique et des Libertés)  3 Place de Fontenoy TSA 80715  75334 PARIS CEDEX 07, Francehttps://www.cnil.fr/Or, in case the subject matter relates to VITEC’s German affiliate:Die Bundesbeauftragte für den Datenschutz und die Informationsfreiheit (BfDI) Husarenstr. 30 53117 BONN, Germanypoststellebfdi.bundde Your AgreementBy submitting data to us and using the website, you agree to our use of your data and of anyone you represent in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy (as amended from time to time, as described above) and you are responsible for ensuring that you have authority to do this on behalf of anyone about whom you submit data to us.Last update September 2019 HomeIndustriesEnterpriseBroadcastMilitary/GovernmentVenuesHouse of WorshipMedicalSolutionsIn-House IPTV Distribution SystemIPTV & Signage Sports Venue SolutionMulti-Site Video StreamingDirect-to-Web & OTT MonitoringContribution & Remote ProductionSituational Awareness & ISRSDK & Custom DesignProductsIPTV & Digital SignageEZ TV PlatformArchivingEncoders & DecodersPortable AppliancesRugged AppliancesopenGear PlatformModular Blade SystemsPCle CardsTranscoders, Media Servers & Gateway SolutionsIP TranscodersDVB GatewayConvertersPortable ConvertersPattern GeneratorsSupportOnline Help DeskRequest Access to Online HelpDeskMaintenance and Support ProgramsMaterial complianceDownloadsCompanyBackgroundLocationsNews & Press ReleasesEventsCareersGreen InitiativeContactBlog HomeNewsEventsSuccess StoriesPrivacy PolicyContact
